Do you realize that four weeks from today we're getting married?
Four weeks, baby!
Four weeks!
Do you realize that you get louder each week?
There's still so much to do.
Have you written your vows yet?
I figured I'd just buy those.
Pat, I'd like to buy a vow.
Sweetie, you know I have no sense of humor when it comes to the wedding.
All right, so have you written yours yet?
No, but I know exactly what I'm going to say.
Do you happen to know exactly what I'm going to say?
All right, let's just do it right now, okay?
Won't be hard.
Just say what's in your heart.
Look at her go.
She must love me more than I love her.
What's wrong with me?
Oh, don't open that door.
So no one told you life was going to be this way?
Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's the old way.
It's like you're always stuck in second gear.
But when it hasn't been your day, week, or month, you've got to start over.
Even though you're here, but I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you too
Monica, there are no words
There are no words!
This should not be this hard
Oh, hey, you've done this before, Ross
Well, what did you say when you made up your vows?
Well, with Carol, I promised never to love another woman until the day I die
She made no such promise
I'm so pathetic
Monica knows what she wants to say
You should have seen her writing and writing and writing
Monica, what? What is the emergency?
You have to help me
I'm supposed to be writing my vows and all I have is this
Well, I like the pretty little drawing of you in the wedding dress
Yeah, except your breasts look kind of small
Those are my eyes
Those are my breasts
Oh, yeah, okay
Why don't you just start with something simple?
Like, um, Monica, from the moment I met you, I knew I loved you
Yeah, I'm not sure I can do that
Everyone, this is Chandler
Hi, I'm Ross' little sister
Okay
Okay, okay, okay
Um, maybe you could start with Chandler, even though we were friends
there was a part of me that always knew I wanted more
Alright, there's a nuclear holocaust
I'm the last man on earth
Would you go out with me?
Oh, are we allowed to lie in the vows?
Or maybe you don't talk about your feelings back then
Maybe you just say something about, you know, all the things that he's taught you, like
Or all the things you taught him
Everybody knows the basic erogenous zones
You got one, two, three, four
Five, six, and seven
There are seven?
That's one?
Kind of an important one
Oh, you know what? I was looking at it upside down
Ah, well, you know, sometimes that helps
Okay, now start out with a little one
A one, a two
A one, two, three
A three
A five
A four
A three, two
Two
A two, four, six
Two, four, six
Four
Two
Four, seven
Five, seven
Six, seven
Seven
Seven, seven, seven
Seven, seven, seven, seven
Oh, I got it
I was saying something like, Monica
Monica
When I look back over our time together
Yeah?
I can't do everything
Look back over your time together
Oh, look, Joanne's
No fair
I don't even have one
How come they get two?
You'll get one
Oh, yeah? When?
All right, I'll tell you what
When we're 40, if neither of us are married
What do you say you and I get together and have one?
Why wouldn't I be married when I'm 40?
Oh, no, no, no
I just meant hypothetically
Okay, hypothetically
Why won't I be married when I'm 40?
No, no, no
No, no, what is it?
Seriously, is there something fundamentally unmarriable about me?
Uh, uh
Well?
Dear God, this parachute is a knapsack
I'm getting married today
Oh, woo-hoo
You think he knew I was here?
Nice try
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Look, Monica
This is not gonna work
But this will work
You are so great, I love you
What?
Nothing, I said, I said you're so great
And then I just, I just stopped talking
You said you love me, I can't believe this
No, I didn't
Yes, you did
You love me
No, I don't
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it
You know, I was thinking, what if I, uh, unpack here?
Then all your stuff would be here
Well?
What if all my stuff was here?
Then you'd be going back and forth all the time, I mean
It doesn't make any sense
Okay
What if we live together and you understand what I'm saying?
You wanted it to be a surprise
Oh my God
Chandler
In all my life
I never thought I would be so lucky
As to fall in love with my best
My best
There's a reason why girls don't do this
Okay, okay, okay, I'll do it
I thought
Wait, I can do this
That it mattered
What I said
Or where I said it
Then I realized
The only thing that matters is that you
You make me happier
Than I ever thought I could be
And if you let me
I will spend the rest of my life trying to make you feel the same way
Monica
Will you marry me?
Yes
Can we come in yet? We're dying out here
Come in, come in
I'm engaged
Hey
Hi
Hey, what have you guys been up to?
Oh, we were helping Chandler write his vows
But he kicked us out because Joey kept making inappropriate suggestions
How is Monica, I love your sweet ass, inappropriate?
How's Monica coming along with her vows?
Let's just say it's lucky she's got a sweet ass
Because she's not so good at the writing
I can't believe this
I can't believe in four weeks they're gonna be married
Well, let's just hope it works
You know, nine out of ten marriages end in divorce
Phoebe, that's not true
Yeah, you're right
How's the missus?
I can't believe they've been together for three years
Has it been that long?
Maybe it seems like less because they hid it from us for so long
Hey, it's me
I'm coming in
I've had a very long, hard day
I'm gonna go get some chicken, you want some?
No thanks, no chicken, bye-bye then
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry, he wouldn't leave
He kept asking me if I wanted chicken
Chicken?
I could eat some chicken
Hey, Jew
Yeah, can I get a three-piece, some coleslaw and some beans and a Coke?
Diet Coke
I don't know why they didn't just tell us
I know, I mean, it's not like we weren't cool about it
You? And you?
Yes, but you cannot tell anyone, no one knows
How? When?
It happened in London
In London?
The reason we didn't tell anyone was because we didn't want to make a big deal out of it
But it is a big deal!
I have to tell someone
You can't
Please, please, we just don't want to deal with telling everyone, okay?
Please, just promise you won't tell
Alright
I can't wait to be with you
I'll just tell Rachel I'm gonna be doing laundry for a couple hours
Laundry, huh? Is that my new nickname?
Aww
You know what your nickname is, Mr. Big
Oh look, there's Monica and Chandler, hey!
Hey, you guys! Hey!
Chandler and Monica! Chandler and Monica!
Oh my God! Chandler and Monica!
Oh my God!
Oh my eyes! My eyes!
Phoebe, Phoebe!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay!
No, they're doing it!
I know, I know!
You know!
Yes, I know, and Joey knows, but Ross doesn't know, so you have to stop screaming!
Hey, what's going on?
What?
Nothing! Oh God, we're just so excited that you might get this apartment!
Actually, it looks really good!
Yeah, it looks pretty good!
Get in here!
Okay, so now they know you know, and they don't know that Rachel knows?
Yes
You know what, it doesn't matter who knows what, now enough of us know that we can just tell them we know!
Now all the lying and the secrets will finally be over!
Or, we could not tell them we know, and have a little son of our own!
Alright honey, we better go, we're gonna catch that movie
Bye!
Bye Chandler!
I miss you already
Okay, did you see that, with the inappropriate and the pinching?
Actually, I did!
Okay, so now do you believe that she's attracted to me?
Oh my God!
Oh my God, she knows about us!
Phoebe knows about us!
Well, I didn't tell them!
Them?
Who's them?
Uh, Phoebe and Joey!
Joey?
And Rachel!
I would have told you, but they made me promise not to tell!
Oh man, they think they are so slick messing with us!
But see, they don't know that we know that they know!
So...
Ah yes, the messers become the messies!
Oh my God, he wants me to come over and feel his bicep and more!
Are you kidding?
No!
I cannot believe he would do that to my...
Wha...
Joey, do they know that we know?
No
Joey!
They know you know
Oh, I knew it!
Oh, I cannot believe those two!
They thought that they could mess with us, they're trying to mess with us!
They don't know that we know they know we know!
And Joey, you can't say anything!
Couldn't if I wanted to!
Listen, this is totally getting out of hand, okay?
She wants me to put lotion on her!
She's bluffing!
No, look, she's not backing down, she went like this!
He's not backing down, he went to get lotion!
Oh man, aren't you guys done yet?
Joey, look, just look at it this way, the sooner Phoebe breaks Chandler, the sooner this is all over and out in the open...
Ooh, I like that
Okay
Oh, okay, show him your bra
He's afraid of bras, can't work them
Wow, you didn't rip off any buttons
Not my first time
You go back out there and you seduce her until she cracks!
Okay, give me a second
Did you clean up in here?
Of course
Oh, you're going?
Um, not without you, lover
So, this is my bra
It's very, very nice
Well, come here
I'm very happy we're going to have all the sex
You should be, I'm very bendy
I'm going to kiss you now
Not if I kiss you first
Well, I guess there's nothing left for us to do but kiss
Here it comes
Our first kiss
Okay, okay, okay, you win
I can't have sex with you
And why not?
Because I'm in love with Monica
You're really in love with Monica
What?
Lover, that's right, I love her
I love her
I love you, Monica
I love you too, Chandler
I thought you guys were doing it, I didn't know you were in love
So that's it, it's over, everybody knows
Well, actually, Ross doesn't
Yes, and we'd appreciate it if no one told him yet
No
What are you doing?
Get off my sister!
You know, your friend's getting married, it's got to change things
You really think it'll be that different?
How could it not be?
I mean, pretty soon they're going to be having kids
And then they're just going to be hanging out with other couples who have kids
And then maybe they're going to have to leave the city
To be near a Volvo dealership
Well, things change
I don't want them to move to a Volvo dealership
It'll be okay, Joe
Sorry, I just, I like things the way they are
Hey, who's this little naked guy?
Uh, that little naked guy would be me
Oh, look at the little thing
Yes
Yes, fine, that is my penis
Can we be grown-ups now?
Who are those people?
Not me
Oh, that's Nana right there, in the middle
Wow
Let's see
Me and the gang at Java Joe's
Wow, Monica, you look just like your grandmother
How old was she there?
Yeah, uh, 24, 25
Huh, looks like a fun gang
Ooh, look, look, look, look, look
I got Monica naked
No, no, that would be me again
Hey, you guys
Hey
What's going on?
Well, we were just talking about you guys getting married and how great it is
Yeah, you can get a Volvo
If that's what you really want
Oh, that's so sweet
So, we both finished our vows
Oh
Can we read them?
Yeah, just as long as I don't hear Taylor's and he doesn't hear mine, okay?
Okay
Oh
Oh, that's beautiful
Oh, funny one, that's a good one
Monica, will you marry me?
What? I don't get it
Oh, yeah
Oh, man, this is hilarious
Chandler
Chandler?
Don't worry, honey, we'll make yours funnier
Dude, I have never known love like this
You really like it?
Dude
How did you write this?
I stole Monica's and changed the name
You can't do that
If he goes first, he can
You